export class Entry {
  question_id: number;
  question: string;
  answer: string;
}

export const DATA: Entry[] = {
    created_at: '07/31/2018 12:00 am EST',
    data: [
        { question_id: 1, question: 'Total Number of Partners', answer: '62' },
        { question_id: 2, question: 'One-time In-Hand', answer: '$7,430.00' },
        { question_id: 3, question: 'One-time Pledged', answer: '$100.00' },
        { question_id: 4, question: 'One-time Total', answer: '$7,530.00' },
        { question_id: 5, question: 'Monthly In-hand', answer: '$1,995.32' },
        { question_id: 6, question: 'Monthly Pledged', answer: '$0.00' },
        { question_id: 7, question: 'Monthly Total', answer: '$1,995.32' },
        { question_id: 8, question: '# of financial partners added this week', answer: '16' },
        { question_id: 9, question: 'How much one time support was pledged this week?', answer: '2510' },
        { question_id: 10, question: 'How much one time support did you receive in-hand this week?', answer: '3160' },
        { question_id: 11, question: 'How much monthly support was pledged this week?', answer: '0' },
        { question_id: 12, question: 'How much monthly support did you receive in-hand this week?', answer: '296' },
        { question_id: 13, question: 'Outstanding Decisions', answer: '3' },
        { question_id: 14, question: '# of new referrals gained this week?', answer: '0' },
        { question_id: 15, question: '# of contacts on hand', answer: '174' },
        { question_id: 16, question: '# of dials', answer: '2' },
        { question_id: 17, question: '# of people talked to', answer: '0' },
        { question_id: 18, question: '# of appointments set up', answer: '0' },
        { question_id: 19, question: '# hours spent making calls', answer: '0' },
        { question_id: 20, question: '# electronic dials', answer: '20' },
        { question_id: 21, question: '# of electronic responses', answer: '10' },
        { question_id: 22, question: '# of appointments set up by e-dials', answer: '7' },
        { question_id: 23, question: '# hours spent on e-dials', answer: '2' },
        { question_id: 24, question: '# of face to face appointments', answer: '6' },
        { question_id: 25, question: '# of group meetings', answer: '1' },
        { question_id: 26, question: '# people at group meetings', answer: '2' },
        { question_id: 27, question: '# hours on appointments', answer: '6' },
        { question_id: 28, question: '# of pre-call letters/postcard sent', answer: '0' },
        { question_id: 29, question: '# of support letters sent', answer: '0' },
        { question_id: 30, question: '# hour spent on correspondence', answer: '1' },
        { question_id: 31, question: '# thank you notes/reminder letters', answer: '16' },
        { question_id: 32, question: '# of total hours spent on MPD this week?', answer: '30' },
        { question_id: 33, question: 'What other MPD work did you do this week?', answer: 'Jesus time, following up for decisions, 13-month report, pre-arrival action points for HQ' },
        { question_id: 34, question: 'Did you talk to your coach this week (phone or Skype, not just texting)?', answer: 'yes' },
        { question_id: 35, question: 'How many modules of Core Doctrine have you completed', answer: '10' },
        { question_id: 36, question: '# hours spent on Core Doctrine this week?', answer: '0' },
        { question_id: 37, question: 'How are you doing?', answer: '3' },
        { question_id: 38, question: 'How can we pray for you?', answer: 'My family just suffered a loss. Pray for peace and comfort.' }
    ]
};
